COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
Die.
Damn!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Hmm... Shadow Clone Jutsu.
And there are quite a few of them.
Here I go!
It's impossible, after all...
There is no way that
you can beat a guy!
There is only one way left
to defeat this guy.
Sasuke!
I see!
So that's your plan, Naruto!
That's pretty good for you!
Demon Wind Shuriken,
Windmill of Shadows...
A Shuriken won't work on me.
I see.
This time it's aiming for my real body...
But...
It's not so easy!
A Shuriken in the Shuriken's shadow!
This is...
The Shadow Shuriken Jutsu!
A second Shuriken in his blind spot!
But...
Still too naive.
He dodged it!
Here it is!
Kakashi the
Sharingan User
You little brat!
Kakashi-sensei!
Naruto...
Your strategy was outstanding.
You've grown up...
Both of you.
The purpose of the Shadow Clones
was not to take down Zabuza,
but to hide my transformation
into Demon Wind Shuriken!
I left one clone behind, then
transformed into Demon Wind Shuriken.
Then a clone threw the real me, who had
transformed into Demon Wind Shuriken,
towards Sasuke!
Sasuke!
When Sasuke got me,
he must have realized
right away who I was.
Then he took out his own Shuriken...
And that's the Shadow Shuriken Jutsu!
Demon Wind Shuriken...
Windmill of Shadows!
Hidden in the shadow of the real Shuriken,
I aimed for Zabuza.
Of course I didn't think
I would defeat Zabuza!
But I thought I'd destroy
the Water Prison.
And as a bonus
I defeated his water clone, too...
It was a huge success!
That was a fluke...
It was a fluke, huh!
Still, they performed outstandingly
in tandem...
in this desperate situation.
Despite the fact...
that those two always
fight like cats and dogs.
Hmph...
I got distracted and
broke my Water Prison Jutsu...
That's not it!
You didn't break the Jutsu...
They forced you to break it.
I'll tell you now,
the same Jutsu won't work on me twice.
So what will you do?
Sakura!
Stay alert.
Sharingan!
Ushi, saru, u.
Ne, inoshishi, Tori, ushi.
Uma, Tori, Ne, Tora.
Inu, Tora, mi, ushi, hitsuji.
Mi, inoshishi, hitsuji Ne...
Ushi, saru, u.
Ne, inoshishi, Tori, ushi.
Uma, Tori, Ne, Tora.
Inu, Tora, mi, ushi, hitsuji.
Mi, inoshishi, hitsuji Ne.
Jin, saru, Tori, tatsu.
Tori, ushi, uma, hitsuji.
Tora, mi, Ne, saru.
U, inoshishi, tatsu, hitsuji.
— Ne, ushi, saru, Tori. Jin, Ne, inoshishi.
— Jin, saru, Tori, tatsu. Tori, ushi, uma, hitsuji.
Tora, mi, Ne, saru.
U, inoshishi, tatsu, hitsuji.
Ne, ushi, saru, Tori.
Jin, Ne, inoshishi.
Tori!
Water Style!
Water Dragon Jutsu!
He copied that chant
in seconds...
and so perfectly...!
W-What is this?
Is it Ninjutsu!
Strange...
What is going on...?
Jin, saru, Tori, tatsu.
Tori, ushi, uma, hitsuji.
Tora, mi, Ne, saru.
U, inoshishi, tatsu, hitsuji.
The Sharingan is the ability to memorize
and copy the enemy's Jutsu...
But...
Tori!
Water Style!
Water Dragon Jutsu!
The Jutsu was set in motion
at the same time!
By any chance, is this guy...
This guy...!
The same identical movement!
Furthermore, at exactly
the same time!
What's going on, Sasuke-kun!
This guy...
My movements...!
He's perfectly...
Reading them.
What?
He's reading my mind?!
Blast him! He's...
giving me
that barren, evil eye... right?
Hah! You're just copying...
You're a pale imitation.
— You won't be able to beat me!
— You!
I'll shut that copycat
monkey-mouth permanently!
W-What's that!
Me?
R-Ridiculous!
Is that his Genjutsu?
Water Style!
Giant Vortex Jutsu!
W-Wha...!
No way!
I was just about to
set forth that Jutsu...
I can't keep up with...
his Jutsu!
It's over...
Why...?
Are you able to see into the future...?
Yeah...
You're going to die!
You were right. He died.
He's definitely dead.
I thank you.
I have been waiting for the chance
to kill Zabuza.
By the looks of that mask...
You're a Tracker Ninja from
the Village Hidden in the Mist.
Impressive. You're very knowledgeable.
Tracker Ninja?
You don't know what
a Tracker Ninja is?
We learned it at
the Academy, didn't we?
Tracker Ninja pursue...
guys like Zabuza who turn against
the village where they were born and raised.
And when they break away from
the village,
Tracker Ninja go after these Rogue Ninja
and assassinate them...
in order to avoid having
the secrets of the village being leaked.
That's common knowledge!
You should study more!
That's right.
I'm a member of Hidden Mist Village's
Tracking Unit
whose mission is to
hunt Rogue Ninja.
From his height and voice,
he's not all that different from Naruto...
A Tracker Ninja...?
He's not just an ordinary kid...
What are you?!
Hey you!
Don't worry, Naruto.
He's not an enemy.
That's not what I'm asking!
I...!
I mean...!
That Zabuza...
That Zabuza was killed!
That guy who was so strong...
He was killed so easily... by a kid
who's no different from me!
We're...
We're pathetic!
I can't accept that!
Well!
I understand your disbelief.
But... this, too, is reality.
In this world, there are kids
who are younger than you...
and stronger than me.
Your battle is over for now.
I must get rid of this corpse...
because it contains many secrets.
Now then, please excuse me.
He's disappeared!
He's not here anymore.
What was all this for?!
What are we anyway?!
Naruto...
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
Things like this happen
when you're a Ninja.
If you're frustrated,
apply it next time!
Our mission hasn't ended yet.
We must take Tazuna-san home.
So sorry, everyone!
You can rest at my house!
Okay!
Let's perk up and go!
W-What!
What happened!
Kakashi-sensei!
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
What'll we do?!
Kakashi-sensei has collapsed!
Gato's henchmen are probably
gonna come and attack us again!
Guess it means we've gotta
fight by ourselves.
Who knows if this training will
make us stronger but,
it's getting interesting!
I'll definitely get stronger.
Next time:
"The Forest of Chakra."
I'm going to kick butt once again!